好吧
Yep.
你好 我是朱迪
Hi. I'm Judy.
- 罗曼 - 我是洛基同事
- Roman. - I worked with Rocky.
对不起
Sorry.
见鬼了一样 对不起 对不起
It's like looking at a ghost. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
搞快走吧
Have to get out of here.
罗曼·艾瑞克
Roman. Eric.
我们应该没见过 但我感觉我好像认识你
We've never met, but I feel like I know you.
我为你的失去深感难过
I'm so sorry for your loss.
需要的话 我都在...
I'm-I'm here if you...
嗷 天啦 你的脸长的
Oh, God. Your face.
其实 看起来不像
It doesn't-- Actually, it doesn't seem like
你在努力做好你的工作 不 看起来...
you are trying to do your job. No, looks like--
你更像是在帮倒忙
It feels like you're doing the opposite of your job
因为 应该非常容易就可以注销掉...
'cause it should be pretty easy to cancel
- 我死去的兄弟的账户 - 你想注销吗？
- my dead brother's account. - Do you want this?
- 我不知道  - 妈 我不知道
- I don't know. - Ma, I don't know.
我正在打电话 不 我不想等！
I'm on the phone. No, do not put me on hold!
- 你想要注销吗？ - 我... 妈 求你了
- Do you want these? - I-- Mom, please.
别跟我说什么别激动！
Don't tell me to fucking calm down!
我都打了差不多一个小时的电话了
I've been on the phone for, like, an hour--
- 喂？操！- 罗曼
- Hello? Fuck! - Roman,
要我帮你留着还是丢掉？
do you want me to keep these or throw them away?
- 我们非得现在弄吗？ - 我们没有房间
- Do we have to do this now? - We don't have the room,
但 如果你什么都想留着...
but if you wanna keep everything--
我们明天再弄不行吗？为什么？
Can we just do this tomorrow, please? Why?
因为我明天就要回去了
Because I'm going back tomorrow.
知道了 但是我还在这里啊 所以就这样吧
Okay, but I'm gonna be here, so just leave it.
你要一个人收拾整个公寓吗？
You're gonna pack up this entire apartment?
- 对 对 - 哦 太有意思了
- Yes. Yes. - Oh, that's rich.
我自己来弄...什么？
I'll do it myself-- What?
我觉得你不该留在这 我觉得
I don't think you should stay here. I don't think
-这对你有好处 -哦 拜托 你不知道
- it's good for you. - Oh, come on. You don't know
妈妈 什么叫对我有好处？你永远不知道
what's good for me, Mom. You never knew
- 什么对我有好处 好吗？- 好吧
- what was good for me. Okay? - All right.
- 你在说笑吗？ - 好吧 那就没关系了
- You kidding me? - Well, then never mind.
- 我不管了  - 很好
- I won't help you. - Good.
- 什么都你自己来弄  - 这就是这么想的
- You can do all this yourself. - That's what I'm saying.
- 那就...走吧 - 我回酒店去
- That's-- Go. - I'll go back to the hotel.
-别给我打电话 -好 这样对你好！
- Don't call me. - Good. Good for fucking you!
够了！
Time-out!
罗曼
Roman.
你需要帮助
You need help.
你才需要帮助
嗯 确实如此
Well, that's true.
大家好
Hello, everyone.
现在七点了 我们开始吧
It's seven o'clock, so I say let's get started.
我发现今天有一些新面孔
I see some new faces here today,
所以我想大家来做一个有趣的绕圈自我介绍
so I thought it would be fun to go in a circle.
说出你的名字
Say your name,
名字首字母相同的蔬菜
a vegetable that starts with the same first letter
还有 别怀念你的同胞胎了
and one thing you don't miss about your twin.
夏洛特 胡萝卜
Charlotte. Carrot.
我一点也不怀念克莱尔抢了我的男朋友那事
I don't miss Claire stealing my boyfriend.
别当真 我开玩笑的
No, I'm kidding.
我开玩笑的 我们不搞绕圈自我介绍
I'm kidding. We won't go in a circle.
但是克莱尔确实抢了我的男朋友
But Claire, she really did steal my boyfriend.
他分不清我们俩 不过还是可以算她抢的 对吧？
He couldn't tell us apart. But it still counts, right?
我怀念她的笑声
I miss her laugh.
我们以前总是一起笑
We always laughed together.
我们还说要模仿艾伯特和科斯特洛来一段双人喜剧
We talked about doing this Abbott and Costello routine.
但我太害羞了
But I was too shy.
所以我对自己说：那我试试单口喜剧好了
So, I said to myself I'll try stand-up.
没错 现在我就要在你们身上试试笑话
Yep, and I'm about to test jokes on you,
请多包涵
so bear with me.
准备好了吗？好
Okay, you ready? All right.
有双胞胎的请举手
Raise your hand if you have a twin.
好的
Okay.
真是一群好观众
This is a good crowd.
很多人总喜欢问
You know, so many people, they're always asking,
“谁大一些？”
"Who's older?"
现在我大一些 因为她已经死了
I am now that she's dead.
作为双胞胎 你会把你和另一半的差异都刻在心里
As a twin, it's like you internalize the difference
你和你的另一半之间
between you and your other half.
克莱尔外向些 克莱尔漂亮些
Claire's the outgoing one, Claire's the beautiful one,
克莱尔感染了衣原体
Claire's the one with chlamydia.
我很伤心
I was so upset
她感染衣原体时我不在
when she got chlamydia without me.
毕竟我们什么都该一起做的嘛
We're supposed to do everything together.
呃 我反正不吃那个 吃起来像球一样
Oh, I wouldn't eat that. Tastes like balls.
嗯 我喜欢吃球
Mm, I like balls.
哦
Oh.
嗯
Mm.
噢 天啦 太糟了
Oh, my God, that's so bad.
你是 呃...
Are you, uh...
我是……？
Am I...?
哦 只是...你说你喜欢吃球 所以……
Oh, just-- You said you like balls, so...
我的兄弟洛基是个同性恋
Rocky, my brother, was gay.
你们是双胞胎？
Was your twin?
嗯...不
Um... No.
好
Right.
这很奇怪 是吧？
It's weird, isn't it?
呃 表观遗传学
Uh, epigenetics.
- 呃... - 它们是你从基因中继承的
- Uh... - They're the things you inherit on top of your DNA.
它们可能会表达偏差
They may account for discrepancies
同卵双胞胎之间
between identical twins.
哈
Huh.
嘿 你晕车吗？
Hey, do you get carsick?
- 有时 为什么？- 哦
- Sometimes. Why? - Oh.
洛奇总是坐在前排
Rocky always had to sit in the front seat
当我们还是孩子的时候 并且...
when we were kids, and...
我不知道 我只是觉得
I don't know, I just thought
这可能与同性恋基因有关
maybe that was connected to, like, the gay gene.
如果有的话
If there is one.
并不是说有这样的人
Not that there is one.
呃 这只是个想法 我不是科学家
Uh, it was just an idea. I'm no scientist.
对 是有同性恋基因
Um, well, there is a gay gene.
我们把橙色看作蓝色 把蓝色看作橙色
Uh, we see orange as blue and blue as orange.
这就是为什么有这么多同性恋
That's why there's so many homosexuals
- 在时尚界 - 哦 对吧？
- in the fashion industry. - Oh. See?
好吧 就这样
Well, there you go.